vafq.org 2009-06-20

# Privacy Policy

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Vafq.org Site. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and Vafq.org which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 

The Information We Collect

Registration Information :-

At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information.")

Publishing Information :-

If you submit any information to Vafq.org to be published on the Site,not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, Trustcode Certificate Profile, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information ("Publishing Information").

Payment Information :-

If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from Vafq.org or a vendor available through Vafq.org, we may collect additional information, such as billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders ("Payment Information").

Statistical Information :-

Vafq.org primary goal in collecting personal or public information is to provide the user with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalization services, interactive communications and many other types of services, most of which are completely free. Business information is used to display the user's business listing or product offerings across our network to fetch maximum business opportunities for the user.

We gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth. ("Statistical Information"). 

Collected Information:-

Publishing Information, Payment Information, Statistical Information and any information we may collect from you through the use of cookies, or any other means, shall collectively be referred to as "Collected Information".

How We May Use Information

We can use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. 

We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

Registration Information :-

We can use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which Vafq.org determines that you might be interested.We may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

Publishing Information :-

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to Vafq.org becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us. 

Payment Information At Vafq.org:

Vafq.org will share your Payment Information with banks or vendors relevant to the transaction in order to enable transactions to be completed. In addition, Vafq.org may use Payment Information to determine your credit-worthiness and, in the process of such determination, Vafq.org may make such Payment Information available to banks or credit agencies.

Any credit card information that you provide through the Site is directly submitted to a payment server of the credit card processing bank. Vafq.org does not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card information. While Vafq.org has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or mis-use. Vafq.org shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other mis-use of Payment Information, including credit card information.

Disclosure of Information :-

We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Vafq.org, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.  
If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Vafq.org or others.

Co-Branded Relationships

We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our Site, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same uniform resource locator, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. In some cases you may be required to submit information for purposes of registering or applying for products or services provided by such third parties or co-branded partners.

The privacy policy of such other parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or co-branded sites. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding to any offers, products or services provided by such other parties. 

Security Measures :-

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not disclose your Password to anyone. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

Changes to Privacy Policy :-

If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Vafq.org in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that Vafq.org return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in Vafq.org possession.

Correcting Your Information :-

You can access, view and edit your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) through your Account with Vafq.org. To update or correct such information, please login at Vafq.org by entering your username and password. 

Feedback at Vafq.org :-

Vafq.org welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to email address of  Vafq.org.

Important Notice:-

Although we adhere to industry standard practices to protect your personal information and confidential data, we cannot ensure that such information and data will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
